W. R. "Bob" Poage Campaign papers, Inclusive: 1898-1997, undated, Bulk: 1936-1978
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Correspondence, 1936-1978; 1
  - Campaign Appreciation Dinner, Waco (4 of 4), 1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Out of District, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Judge W.M.C. Black Case, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Out of District, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - 1972 Campaign, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Presidential Campaign, George McGovern vs. Richard Nixon, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Campaign (1 of 4), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Campaign (2 of 4), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Campaign (3 of 4), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Campaign (4 of 4), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Contributions (1 of 6), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Contributions (2 of 6), 1972 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Contributions (3 of 6), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Contributions (4 of 6), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Contributions (5 of 6), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Contributions (6 of 6), 1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Funds Refunds, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Georgetown 4-P Party, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Letters, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Letters, Agriculture, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Letters, Friends of Poage, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Letters, Responses of Support, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - 1972 Campaign, Concerning Murray Watson (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Campaign, Newspaper Announcements and Accounts, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Campaign, Radio Announcement Requests and Scripts, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Thank You Letters, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Constituent Congratulations and Appreciation, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - General Congratulations, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - District, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Gatesville/Belton, Mary Hardin-Baylor Visits, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Marlin Appreciation Dinners, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Out of District, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Volunteer Workers, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Contributions (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Contributions (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Contributions (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - District, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Military and Veterans Facilities, District, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - New Counties in Eleventh District, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Out of District, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Taylor Barbeque, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - 1974 Campaign, 1973-1975 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Campaign, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Announcements Requests and Accounts, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - 1974 Campaign, Concerning Postcards (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Campaign Contributions, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Congratulations, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - District, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Hearne City Bribe Accusation (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Hearne City Bribe Accusation (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Out of District, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - General, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - District, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Excess Campaign Funds Donation, Poage Library, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Out of District, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Appreciation Dinners, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Jack Burgess Debate Challenge, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Campaign (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Campaign (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Letters to Democratic County Officials, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Campaign Letters, Waco Friends, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Letters, Friends of Ruth Lair, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Letter Responses, Waco Friends, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - 1976 Campaign, Richard Thornburg (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Strategy, Staff, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Colleagues and Democratic Committees, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Congratulations (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Congratulations (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Congressional Politics, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Jack Burgess, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Department of Justice Investigation, 1972 Campaign Account, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - District, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - District Events and Appreciation Dinners, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Announcement Accounts, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Out of District, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Presidential Nominees and Campaign, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Proposed Debates, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Recommendations for Political Appointments (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Recommendations for Political Appointments (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Financial Contributions, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Jack Burgess, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Campaign 1978, Poage’s Advice and Involvement, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - District, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Out of District, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Rumors of Resignation and Retirement Announcement, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - South Africa Trip Investigation, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - 1978 Campaign, Poage’s Advice and Involvement (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Out of District, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Poage Library Donations and Retirement, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Retirement, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Financial Documents, 1935-1978; 2
  Series II. Financial Documents, the smallest series in the collection, contains a wide array of financial materials relating to Representative Bob Poage's election campaigns. Some of the most common records found in this series include receipts of campaign expenses, reports filed with the Clerk of the House of Representatives, and income tax reports. Poage also filed expenditure reports submitted by his political opponents. While the series covers the entirety of Poage's political career in Washington, D.C., most of the materials are from the 1970's, Poage's final decade in office. This series is arranged chronologically and is in good condition.
  - Ledger, Contributions and Expenses, 1936 Campaign, 1935-1936 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Frank Tirey Campaign, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Statements of Campaign Expenses, 1936 Campaign (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Campaign Expenses, 1940 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Statements, 1942 Campaign (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence and Statements, 1944 Campaign (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Expense Reports, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Expenditure Reports, 1950 Campaign (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Filing Fees and Campaign Expenses, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Filing Fees and Campaign Expenses (1 of 2), 1954 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Filing Fees and Campaign Expenses (2 of 2), 1954 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Campaign Announcements, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, W. R. Poage Campaign Account, 1964-1976 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Ledger, Campaign Account, 1965-1977 July (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Poage Election Campaign Accounts, Notebook (1 of 2), 1965-1976 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Poage Election Campaign Accounts, Notebook (2 of 2), 1965-1976 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - 1972 Income Tax Reports, W. R. Poage Campaign Account, 1972-1977 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - 1972 Reports Filed with Clerk of the House (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - 1972 Reports Filed with Clerk of the House (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Campaign Fund Committees, Washington, D.C., 1972 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Charts on the Economy, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Check Stubs, Campaign Account, 1972-1974 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Common Cause Campaign Funds Analysis, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Expenditure Reports, 1972 Primary Election (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Expenditure Reports, Bob Poage for Congress: Temple Committee, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Expenditure Reports, McLennan County Committee for Poage, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Expenditure Reports, Murray Watson, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Expenditures, 1972 Campaign (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Filing Fee Documents, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Poage Campaign Account, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Reports, State Campaign Fund, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - W. R. Poage Campaign Fund, 1972 Campaign (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - 1973 Income Tax Reports, Bob Poage, 1973-1976 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - 1973 Reports Filed with Clerk of the House (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - 1974 Income Tax Reports, W. R. Poage Campaign Account, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Expenditure Reports, Texas Campaign, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Expenditures, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - State Reports, 1974 Campaign, 1973-1975 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - 1974 Reports Filed with Clerk of the House (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - 1975 Reports Filed with Clerk of the House, 1974-1976 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Expenditure Reports, Connie Lawson, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Expenditure Reports, Donald Wayne Clements, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Expenditure Reports, Laurel N. Dunn, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Expenditures, 1974 Campaign (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence and Expenditures, 1976 Campaign, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Expenditure Reports, Common Cause, 1975-1976 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Expenditures, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Ledger, W. R. Poage Campaign Committee, 1975 December-1977 April (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - 1975 Income Tax Reports, Poage Campaign, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - 1976 Reports Filed with Clerk of the House, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Campaign Accounts, Baylor Donation, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Committee Contributions, 1976 Campaign (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Committee Contributions, 1976 Campaign (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Expenditure Reports, 1976 Campaign, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Expenditure Reports, Burgess for Congress Committee, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Expenditure Reports, Steve Alexander, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Expenditures, Poage Campaign Account, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Expense Report, Jack Burgess, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Federal Election Commission Reports, W. R. Poage Campaign Committee, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Quarterly Reports, Bob Poage, 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Quarterly Reports, W. R. Poage Campaign Committee, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Expenditure Reports, Friends of Jack Burgess Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Expenditure Reports, Jack Burgess, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Expenditure Reports, Leath for Congress, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Expenditure Reports, Olson for Congress Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Subject Files, 1918-1981, undated; 3
  Series III. Subject Files, formerly referred to as Reference Files in past finding aids, are a collection of materials accumulated by Representative Bob Poage and his staff relating to specific topics of interest. These include aspects of his own campaigns, the rise of national figures such as Adlai Stevenson and Lyndon B. Johnson, election results divided up by county, Poage's political rivals including Lane Denton and Murray Watson, voting records, and materials relating to Poage's retirement from the U.S. House in 1978. The series is arranged alphabetically by topic or material type and is in good condition.
  - 1936 Campaign, Guide for Texas Democratic Primary and General Elections (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - 1940 Campaign, Advertising, circa 1940 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - 1940 Campaign, Broadcasting (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - 1940 Campaign, Clippings (1 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - 1940 Campaign, Clippings (2 of 3) (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - 1940 Campaign, Clippings (3 of 3) (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - 1940 Campaign, Concerning Advertising Folders (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - 1940 Campaign, County Mailing Lists, 1939-1941 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - 1940 Campaign, Directory of Post Offices, Eleventh Congressional District, 1940 June (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - 1940 Campaign, Lists of Correspondents, 1940, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - 1940 Campaign, Rally Thursday, Correspondence, 1940 July (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - 1940 Campaign, Speeches Endorsing Poage (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - 1940 Democratic Campaign, Clippings, 1937-1940 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - 1944 Campaign, Clippings, 1943-1944, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - 1944 Campaign, Press Releases and Statements (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - 1946 Campaign, Clippings (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - 1946 Campaign, Mailing Lists (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 1948 Campaign, Statistics, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - 1950 Campaign, Clippings (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - 1950 Campaign, Certificate of Election (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - 1950 Campaign, Forms and Promotional Materials, 1950, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - 1950 Campaign, Poll Tax Counts (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - 1950 Campaign, Sample Ballot, 1950 July 22 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - 1950 Campaign, Speeches (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign, General (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - 1960 Presidential Campaign, Agricultural Issues, 1958-1960 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - 1968 Campaign, Clippings (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - 1972 Campaign, “An Opinion Study of Potential Voters in the Eleventh Congressional District”, 1971 December (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - 1972 Campaign, Campaign Presentation (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - 1972 Campaign, Caravan (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - 1972 Campaign, Clippings (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - 1972 Campaign, Literary Productions (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - 1972 Campaign, Press Releases (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - 1974 Campaign, Literary Productions, 1972-1975 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - 1976 Campaign, Advertising, 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - 1976 Campaign, Clippings (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - 1978 Campaign, Clippings (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - 1978 Campaign, Literary Productions, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Adlai Stevenson, Clippings, General, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Adlai Stevenson, Clippings, The Democrat, 1952 November 1 (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Adlai Stevenson, Literary Productions and Pamphlets, 1950-1952 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Adlai Stevenson, Literary Productions, Democratic National Committee (1 of 2), 1952 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Adlai Stevenson, Literary Productions, Democratic National Committee (2 of 2), 1952 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Adlai Stevenson, Press Releases and Statements, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - American Conservative Union, Endorsement, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - American Federationist, Periodical, 1943 June (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Announcements, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Awards, Clippings, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Background Research for Speeches, 1943-1944 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Belden Poll, Public Opinion Survey, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Bell County, Temple, “Poage Day” and Dinner, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Binder, Town List for 1974 Eleventh District Composition (1 of 4), 1973 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Binder, Town List for 1974 Eleventh District Composition (2 of 4), 1973 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Binder, Town List for 1974 Eleventh District Composition (3 of 4), 1973 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Binder, Town List for 1974 Eleventh District Composition (4 of 4), 1973 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Bob Krueger, Correspondence and List of Contributors, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Bob Poage Appreciation Dinner, Correspondence and Logistical Materials, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Bob Poage for Congress: Temple Committee, Correspondence and Financial Documents, 1972-1974 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Brownwood Appreciation Dinner, Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Buster Brown, Clippings, 1945, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Appreciation Dinner, Temple Scrapbook, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Campaign District Tours, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Campaign Envelopes and Letterhead, circa 1970’s (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Campaign Mailing List, Local Candidates, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Campaign Support Lists for Temple, Texas, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Candidate Lists, Correspondence and Rosters, 1944 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Certificate of Election, 1974 November 22 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Clarence Elwell, Lists from 1940 Campaign, 1939-1940 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Clipping, Temple Daily Telegram, “In Appreciation of Congressman W. R. (Bob) Poage”, 1971 October 18 (Box 59 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1942, undated (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1977 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Connie Lawson, Clippings and Correspondence, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - County Delegates, Clippings, 1944 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Dan Kubiak, Clippings and Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Declaration of Candidate Forms, 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Candidates, Clippings and Reports, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Democratic Congressional Dinner, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - The Democratic Digest, 1944 August-September (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Democratic National Committee, Reports, 1943-1944 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Election Filing, District Lists, 1942 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths, 1946 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths, 1952 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (1 of 2), 1958 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (2 of 2), 1958 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (2 of 2), 1960 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (1 of 2), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (2 of 2), 1964 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (1 of 3), 1966 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (2 of 3), 1966 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (3 of 3), 1966 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (1 of 3), 1968 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (2 of 3), 1968 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (3 of 3), 1968 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (1 of 3), 1972 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (2 of 3), 1972 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths (3 of 3), 1972 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Election Filing, Loyalty Oaths, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Election Returns, General, 1934-1936 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Election Returns, General, 1944 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Election Returns, General, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Election Returns, Bell County, General, 1944-1976 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Election Returns, Bell County, Precincts (1 of 2), 1934-1976 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Election Returns, Bell County, Precincts (2 of 2), 1934-1976 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Election Returns, Bosque County, General, 1934-1976 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Election Returns, Bosque County, Precincts, 1934-1976 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Election Returns, Brown County, 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Election Returns, Burnet County, 1972-1976 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Election Returns, Coleman County, 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Election Returns, Comanche County, 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Election Returns, Coryell County, 1934-1976 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Election Returns, Coryell County, 1934-1976 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Election Returns, Eleventh Congressional District, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Election Returns, Eleventh Congressional District, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Election Returns, Erath County, 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Election Returns, Falls County, General, 1930-1976 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Election Returns, Falls County, Precincts, 1930-1976 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Election Returns, Hamilton County, 1972-1976 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Election Returns, Hood County, 1966-1976 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Election Returns, Lampasas County, 1972-1976 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Election Returns, Limestone County, 1966-1970 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Election Returns, McCulloch County, 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Election Returns, McLennan County, General, 1924-1976 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Election Returns, McLennan County, Precincts #1-17, 1924-1976 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Election Returns, McLennan County, Precincts #18-55, 1924-1976 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Election Returns, Milam County, General, 1930-1976 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Election Returns, Milam County, Precincts, 1928-1976 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Eligio de la Garza, Clippings, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Endorsements for Poage, Clippings and Correspondence, 1938-1939 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Endorsements for Poage, Eleventh Congressional District, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Federal Corrupt Practices and Political Activities, Legislative Bill, 1950 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Federal Election Campaign Act of 1971, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Frank Tirey Campaign, Clippings, 1936, undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Frank Tirey Campaign, Legal Documents, 1918-1936 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Frank Tirey Campaign, Rosters and Voting Records, 1936 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Frank Tirey Campaign, Speeches (1 of 2), 1936 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Frank Tirey Campaign, Speeches (2 of 2), 1936 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Friends of Lane Denton for Congress Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Friends of the Eleventh District, Announcement, 1974 January 17 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Hubert Humphrey, Trip to Waco, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Jack Burgess, Clippings (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Jack Burgess, Clippings (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Jack Burgess, Clippings (1 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Jack Burgess, Clippings (2 of 2), 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Jack Burgess, Literary Productions and Press Releases, 1973-1976 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Jack Burgess and Marvin Leath Debates, Clippings, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - John Bates, Advertisements and Clippings, 1950 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Johnson Administration, Factbook, “The Johnson Administration Record: First Session of the 89th Congress, January 4-October 23, 1965”, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Lane Denton, Clippings, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Lane Denton, Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Lane Denton, Statement of Candidate, 1977-1978 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Lloyd Bentsen, Clippings, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson, Inauguration Materials, 1964-1965 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Lyndon Olson, Jr., Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Mailing Lists, Government Officials and Organizational Officers (1 of 2), 1945-1948 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Mailing Lists, Government Officials and Organizational Officers (2 of 2), 1945-1948 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Mailing Lists, Local Officials and Supporters, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Marvin Leath, Clippings (1 of 3), 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Marvin Leath, Clippings (2 of 3), 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Marvin Leath, Clippings (3 of 3), 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - McLennan County Committee for Poage, Correspondence and Financial Documents, 1972-1974 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Murray Watson, 1972 Primary (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Murray Watson, Clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Murray Watson, Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Murray Watson, Resolutions, 1967-1968 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - National Alliance of Senior Citizens, Endorsement, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - National Conservative Action Committee, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers, Accounts and Statement Requests, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 6)